The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
10 years ago
Stop running !
Stop him !
Stay where you are !
Hand over the bell and I'll spare your life !
Stop !
I'll handle this.
Zhao Guo\NRogue cultivator\N10th layer of Qi Condensation
Young Master Teng, this is my family heirloom,
it's useless to you !
Teng Li\N14th layer of Qi Condensation
Even if it's useless,
I still I want it !
Hand it over ! Now !
Hurry !
Are the lives of low level cultivators like me
worthless to you !?
Give it !
Li'er greets Grandfather.
My dear grandson,
you're the heir of the Teng Family.
You can take whatever you want.
All the treasures under this sky are yours.
What's wrong with this place ?
My Divine Sense is locked at 300 meters...
After I flatten this place,
you won't have anywhere to hide !
What the hell !?
You won't trap me !
Scram !
Now's the time !
You dared to ambush me...
Damn it !
When I catch you,
I'll make you suffer !
I'll extract your soul
and I will refine it until you die !
Senior !
Relax, I'm not dead yet.
This brat is a hundred times more talented than you.
He never had to struggle
and was fed with a silver spoon.
Without that artifact he had,
he'd be dead already.
I had to destroy that artifact he had in order to kill him.
It's okay,
we're just getting started.
Little Lin, what are you looking for ?
Found it.
There you are.
Why did you stop running ?
You have nowhere to escape to !
Senior, help me !
What is this stench ?
Another one of his schemes !
Wu Yu's Corpse
A Green Core ?
I never thought someone would cultivate the Green Core Method.
This is nothing like a Golden Core.
It's an explosive
with devastating power.
Luckily, we're far enough.
This looks like a semi-sentient Corpse Puppet.
How did you know it was here ?
I sensed that all the spiritual energy
was converging towards here.
But strangely,
the closer we got,
the sparser the Blue Thread Vines.
So...
I guessed that this place hides
something even the vines fear.
That brat is probably just fleeing now.
Since he gave up chasing you,
it's time to counterattack.
Trying to run ?
I won't let you.
Your lowly life
isn't worth enough to die together !
He's gambling
on whose sword is faster.
I can still teleport you, don't risk it !
Teng Li will die today !
Madman !
You're insane !
Die !
Senior !
Note: A bag of holding is basically a transportable compressed space used for storage.
Kid, you were reckless.
Had I been slower,
you'd be dead !
This was my only chance to kill Teng Li.
If I had missed it
and allowed him to recover,
it would've been over.
But that gamble was too risky !
It wasn't a gamble.
He was exhausted
and couldn't outspeed my sword.
Wang Lin,
I feel like I met a new you today.
Even I might not have dared
to gamble like that.
Will it work if I use Foundation Stealing on him ?
Perfectly.
He reached Late stage Foundation Establishment at such a young age
and his talent is exceptional.
Senior, please guard me while I use your method.
If you kill me,
my grandfather will hunt you !
Grandfather, save me !
Li'er !
Who is it ?!
Stop !
If you spare my grandson's soul
I promise to spare you !
He killed my friend
and tried to kill me.
He's evil.
He isn't dying meaninglessly,
but helping my cultivation.
If you dare to kill my grandson
and scatter his soul,
even if I need to search the whole planet,
I, Teng Huayuan, will take your life !
Li'er !!!
Ancestor...
don't waste your Nascent Soul's Soul Blood !
I swear that
I will search heaven and earth
and I will avenge you !
Curse,
go !
activate !
Whoever kills a Teng
shall suffer Teng Huayuan's curse !
A Nascent Soul cultivator cursed you at great cost.
If you get too close to him
he will teleport to you instantly.
Senior,
is there any way to break this curse ?
Don't panic.
Just keep your distance.
Since I'm with you,
he will never be able to find you.
Now,
to continue to cultivate
you need to find an extreme Yin energy gathering spot.
Cultivate the Underworld Ascension Method I taught you.
You...
Senior !
Teng Huayuan had a jade that cracked when Teng Li died. It's very common for sects or families to have objects that represent the life of a disciple. The disciple will leave a part of his Divine Sense inside it so that when he dies, the Divine Sense will vanish to inform of his death. Most of the time it will be a jade slip or a lamp.
I've been walking this path for endless years
just to catch a glimpse of your silhouette.
Is it the compass of fate
that wrote this outcome for us ?
The heavens want to erase your existence,
that's the obsession guiding me.
Is this the path to uncover
truths from falsehoods ?
In a world of murk and shadow,
only the flame of truth can light the way.
Look at them all,
being carried by the waves.
being drowned.
I don't want to believe in whoever decides fate,
I will let the world refine my soul.
So what if I become an Immortal and defy the heavens ?
I will fight.
I'll break through the abyss of despair
to finally learn who I really am.
My body is stained by the bloody color of slaughter,
I embrace this obsession.
I won't glance back at the wasteland I left behind.
Even if this suffering shatters my soul
and I'm reborn countless times in hell,
I'll still fight.
It's hard to avoid loneliness
when you are above everyone else.
Can a moth that has witnessed the flames of a Suzaku
be afraid of a firefly ?